<result>
	<resultCode>0</resultCode> 
	<resultMsg>Success</resultMsg>
	<startNum>1</startNum>
	<endNum>16</endNum>
	<isEndOfList>true</isEndOfList>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003202866</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[ClockFace]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.app.clockface</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003202866/IconImage_20251020052001579_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[2.2.68.0]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>226800000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>87621946</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>REQUEST_DELETE_PACKAGES||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||SUBSTITUTE_SHARE_TARGET_APP_NAME_AND_ICON||INSTALL_PACKAGES||INTERNET||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||REQUEST_IGNORE_BATTERY_OPTIMIZATIONS||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v3.4.00.4>
※ v3.4.x supports One UI 8 and above devices.
Added battery optimization exception for better clock display in ClockFace

<v3.3.08.19>
The phenomenon of icons being exposed has been fixed.

<v3.3.08.15>
※Version 3.3.X supports the One UI 7 or higher device. 
-10 new watch presets have been added.
-Minor bug fixes and stability improvements have been made.

<v3.3.7.1>
 - One UI 7.0 and later devices

<v3.1.7.1>
※Version 3.1.X supports the One UI 6 device. 
[Added] - One UI 6.1 and later devices
     - Support for new fonts.
     - Added a weather item.
     - Support for frames on images (including GIFs). (One UI 6.0~)
[Changed]
※Devices that do not support "clock style" due to integration between lock screen and AOD will only support "Lock screen" clock style in this app.

<3.0.08.0>
- Updated a wearable plugin version in One UI 6

<v3.0.07.0>
- One UI 6 support
- Added Japanese language support

□ One UI 5
<V2.3.23>
※ Z Flip3 / Z Flip4
 - Stabilization of clock style menu entry.

<v2.3.19>
 - Fixed the error that some existing clocks were forced to change after the app patch (v2.3.18) in order to keep the previous clocks.
    ※ Notice for users who installed v2.3.18
     1. Clocks created in v2.3.18 will be restored to the previous palette (first time only).
     2. If you applied the sample clock provided in v2.3.18, it will revert to the sample clock of the previous version (v 2.3.6)(first time only).

<v2.3.18>
- support Zflip5 clocks.
- support clear background on Image item.
- added gif search(tenor).

<v2.3.06.0>
- Add GTS backup and restore (It will be working with GTS newer version.)

□ One UI 3/4
<v2.2.68>
- Fixed the issue that Clock style is not updated at times

<v2.2.57> 
- Supported device extension and fix minor bugs

<v2.2.31.2>
- Available in One UI 4 based on Android 12

□ One UI 1/2
<v1.2.09>
Pre-preparation for OneUI 3]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Pick a clock style you like!

[ONE UI 6.1]
added font/weather item ( From S24 models)
added framed image(GIF) item.

[ONE UI 6.0]
added framed image(GIF) item.

[ONE UI 5.0]
Support Tablet ( From Galaxy Tab S8)

[ONE UI 4.1]
Connect a Galaxy Watch to preview more watch faces (※ However, created by Watch Face Studio)

[One UI 3]
Create a clockface to your taste. 
You can select the clockface style and decorate it by adding text, images and GIFs.
Enjoy your own clockface on Lockscreen and AOD
 - Create clockface: You can change the style and color of an hour hand, minute hand, pin, background, etc.
 - Apply the clockface on Lockscreen and AOD


[Target]
- Android 9/10/11 SAMSUNG devices.

[Language]
- Korean
- English
- Simplified Chinese
#5]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000004772683</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Home Up]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.app.homestar</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000004772683/IconImage_20251030024917363_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[13.0.00.47]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>1300000047</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>23332808</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>READ_WALLPAPER_INTERNAL||MANAGE_APP_PREDICTIONS||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||ACCESS_SHORTCUTS||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||INTERNAL_SYSTEM_WINDOW||REORDER_TASKS</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<17.0.00.48>
※ Supports devices with One UI 8 and above.
- Bug fix for the widget content appearing larger than expected when using DIY Home.
- Fixed other bugs.

<17.0.00.40>
-Added tablet device support.
※When creating a desktop workspace on tablets, the Task Changer layout is fixed to the default type to maintain task switching usability.
-Other bug fixes and stability improvements.
<v17.0.00.32>
*Supported Devices: One UI 8 and above
*DIY Home Screen
- Alignment Guide Lines: Guides for aligning items
- App Launch Animation Settings: Animations for overlapping items
- Item Group Editing: Easy editing with grouping and ungrouping
- Item Edit Lock: Prevents accidental changes with a lock feature
- Sticker Action Function: App integration and touch animations
- Floating Toolbar: Joystick feature for easy home screen editing

*Home Screen
-Page Indicator Hiding: Enables a clean home screen layout
-Horizontal Scroll: Supports horizontal scrolling in 'Alphabetical Order' mode
-HomeUp Quick Access: Pop-up menu on home screen and recent apps

*Edge Panel
-Launch Apps in Selected View Type: Full, split, and pop-up screen types

*Gesture Settings
-App Launch Animation Tuning Supported

<v16.0.0.90>
- (Z Fold) Support DIY Home function when cover screen mirroring is on
- (Tablet) Remove 'show favorites' setting menu

<v16.0.0.86>
- Fold and tablet devices have been added to HomeUp support.
- Fixed floating taskbar display bug.
- Fixed other bugs

<v16.0.0.72>
- Fixed flickering issue on the home screen while using DIY Home
- Fixed widget errors while using DIY Home
- Fixed other bugs

<v16.0.0.60>
-Fixed a bug where widget updates were not applied after changing wallpapers while using DIY Home
- Improved handling of nested items when moving them in DIY Home edit mode
- Fixed other bugs

<v16.0.00.58>
- Fixed the 'OneUI Home' force close issue due to conflict with specific resource when entering homescreen editing screen while using DIY home screen
- Fixed bugs where widgets remain transparent when deleting widgets using toolbar in DIY homescreen edit mode
- Fixed some bugs

<v16.0.00.56>
□ Home Up has been redesigned!
 - New Feature
  · DIY Home
  · Home gesture Animation tuning
  · Edge panel

<v15.0.01.19>
  : The following features are added to the upgraded devices with OneUI 6.1
   - Home screen - 'Access Finder' (including S24)
   - Home screen - 'App Icon Setting' (including S24)
   - Folder - 'Apply folder background color'
   - Folder - 'Apply folder background blur adjustment'
   - Folder - 'Folder icon arrangement'
    ※ Unsupported functions in the S24 device group will be provided through the 'One UI Home' app update. 

v15.0.00.11
※The issues are only fixed when the latest One UI Home (15.0.05.5 or later) is installed.
   - Fixed an issue where settings were reset when deleting an app.
   - Added the unsupported layouts for Task Changer

v15.0.00.7
- Partial opening of One UI 6.0 support
  ▷ Upcoming features
    1. Home screen - 'Apps List'
    2. Home screen - 'Finder Access '
    3. Task Changer - 3 types of unsupported layout (Stack, Vertical List, Slim List)
  ▷  Deleted features
    1. Folder - 'Folder title suggestion'
    2. Folder - Folder Grid- 'Folder Icon'
    3. Task Changer - 'Allow recent app gestures in the pay region home screen '

<v14.0.0.31>
- Fixed some errors 

<v14.0.0.29>
- Fixed bug that change the folder grid after rebooting
- Fixed the grid setting bug of the cover screen in Fold device.
- Fixed some errors 

<v14.0.0.12>
 - This is available only for One UI 5

<v13.0.00.47>
- Fixed some errors 

<v13.0.00.43>
- Support One UI 4.1.1
- Fixed the number error of Direct Share

<v13.0.00.39>
- Disable the Favorites Maximum Count menu on the Tablet device (up to 14 are supported by default)
- Fixed some errors

<v13.0.00.35>
- Fixed the display error of folder after S OS upgrade in Tablet
- Increased the maximum number of favorites to 12 in Foldable device.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[7]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Enjoy enhanced One UI Home experience.

HOME UP!

HomeUp is the extension edition of One UI Home.

1. Redesign your homescreen with DIY Home 
2. Create your own gestures animation
3. Use various layouts in home screen, apps and folder
4. Customize Popup folder styles and layouts
5. Restore homescreen layout
6. Customize recent app window type 
7. Customize your Edge panels
8. Edit Share-via window

※ App permissions
The following permissions are required for the app service. You can still use the app's basic functions without allowing the optional permissions.

[Required permission]
- Storage(Photos and videos) : Access to Storage is required to back up the preview screen and layout. (Android 14 or lower)
[optional permission]
- Phone: Used to read phone status and identifier information (Android 14 or lower)

<HOME_HOMESTAR:3001:6100>]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000005293390</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Keys Cafe]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.keyscafe</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000005293390/IconImage_20251110035747591_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[1.7.00.12]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>170000012</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>79858088</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||READ_MEDIA_IMAGES||VIBRATE||WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE||INTERNET||WRITE_MEDIA_IMAGES||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE||WRITE_SETTINGS</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<1.8.00.13>  
Starting with One UI 8, meet the new face of Kids Cafe.  
Based on valuable feedback from keyboard users, more convenient and fun features have been added.  
※This version is first available on select devices with One UI 8 and will be rolled out gradually.
✔️Main Update Contents  
1. Revamped UI and Home Screen  
 - Changed to a more intuitive design  
 - View my usage statistics on the home screen:  
  Today's input statistics, common typos, most frequently used word today, word canvas  
2. Enhanced Keyboard Customization  
 - Expanded customization of key colors  
 - Added gesture motion customization feature  
3. New Gesture Customization Features  
 - Quickly execute functions with two-finger or three-finger gestures  
 - Provide gesture design usage  
4. Stability improvements and bug fixes  


■ One UI 7.0
<v1.7.0.12>
* Bug fixes
Make your own keyboard
- Fixed issue that can't be entered when setting Korean Moa Keyboard
- Fixed issue that  Up, Down, Left and Right Flick Not worked

<v1.7.0.11>
- Applied One UI 7.0 stabilization code
- Fixed issue where apps occasionally crashed
- Fixed issue where themed keyboard appeared in an outdated version
- Fixed issue where badges were displayed incorrectly in the keyboard editing screen
- Other UI and operation errors improved

<v1.6.1.11>
※ Versions v1.6.X.X support One UI 6.
- Some basic theme visibility issues have been improved.

<v1.6.1.10>
- Theme optimization for One UI 6.1

* Bug fixes
- Improvement of app interruption phenomenon
 Correct errors while selecting images from my own sticker
 Correct errors on the key effect screen
 Correct typing practice start screen error
- Correct progress bar errors related to key size in keyboard editing
- Fix key error where key label is empty
- Correct errors that cannot be entered with Chinese keyboard in my own keyboard creation save menu
- Fix the problem that occurred when the device was rotated in the keyboard creation dialog

■ One UI 6.0
<v1.6.0.9>
 - Applied stabilization code of One UI 6.0.
 - Create Keyboards at low resolution - Editing Keyboards has fixed problems that are difficult to edit because the keyboard size is too large.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Set up a keyboard that’s tailored to you.

You can increase the sizes of keys that you have trouble pressing and map your favorite emoticons to locations of your choosing.
Add effects to your keyboard making it fun to type on, or change your keyboard’s color to one you like, or change your keyboard's touch sound.
Improve your typing skills while enjoying the keyboard game.
You can edit and save the photos you want, make them into stickers, and use them on the Samsung keyboard.
Some advanced options for Samsung keyboards are provided.

[Key Features]
■ One UI 4.1.1
- Make your own Split Keyboard (for One UI 4.1.1, Galaxy Fold ※ Samsung Keyboard v5.5.0.47 or later)
   This is key feature for Galaxy Fold users. You can edit split keyboard via Keys Cafe.

■ One UI 4.1
- My Sticker
Keys Cafe launches my own sticker. Make images from Gallery into a unique sticker and express your meanings~
※ Samsung Keyboard v5.4.65.0 or later is supported

■ One UI 4.0
- Keyboard advanced settings
Provides advanced functions related to Samsung Keyboard.

■ OneUI2.5
- Changing the sizes of keys: You can adjust the heights and widths of keys.
- Remapping keys: You can remap keys or add new keys.
- Setting up a keyboard theme: You can set up a color or effect for your keyboard. (OneUI2.1 not supported)
- Gaming on your keyboard: Playing game and see scores and ranking

※Keys Cafe works from Samsung keyboard version 5.1.05.9

#GoodLockFriends #0]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003002072</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[LockStar]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.systemui.lockstar</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003002072/IconImage_20251020051337588_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[3.0.00.32]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>300032000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>64610116</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>FOREGROUND_SERVICE||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS||MEDIA_CONTENT_CONTROL||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS_FULL||REQUEST_IGNORE_BATTERY_OPTIMIZATIONS||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS||WAKE_LOCK||MANAGE_USERS||MANAGE_ACTIVITY_STACKS||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||MANAGE_FINGERPRINT||USE_BIOMETRIC_INTERNAL||BIND_APPWIDGET||SET_WALLPAPER||WRITE_SETTINGS||ACCESS_KEYGUARD_SECURE_STORAGE</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v7.0.01.10>  
- Fixed intermittent errors that may occur during package updates.  
- Resolved notification display issues on the tablet's horizontal lock screen. 

<v7.0.01.9>
※ Available only on One UI 8 or higher
- Fixed malfunction of Fold 7 cover screen AOD (unable to add widgets and stickers, brightness adjustment malfunction)
- Fixed lock screen widget errors.

<v7.0.01.5>
※ Supports One UI 8 devices.
-Fixed the issue where the responsive clock was not functioning.
-Improved loading errors for the lock screen widget.
-Corrected the icon display error while using the 'Extend Unlock' feature.

<v7.0.00.14>
- Supports devices for One UI 7.0
- Integrated the LockStar settings screen with the preload lock screen editor

<v6.1.00.18>
- Fixed the issue of clock display and editing in the LockStar app on Flip 6
- Other errors improved

<v6.1.0.11>
- Supports devices upgraded to One UI 6.1
  ※ The following functions require an update to AOD version v8.7.99.11 or later and are not available on devices supporting "Full Screen AOD" (e.g., s24)
    1) Edit AOD function
    2) AOD manual brightness option


v.6.1.00.4
[Changes]
The widget can be freely moved from the bottom fixed position.
※ From One UI 6.1, this app only supports the 'lock screen' on devices where the operation between the lock screen and AOD is integrated.

v.6.0.0.5
- Fixed an issue that did not show the settings for a widget at times
- Improve the app performance

v.6.0.0.4
- OneUI 6 support

v.5.1.0.25
- Added stabilization behavior for widgets
- Fixed an issue where the face recognition VI would not stop

v5.1.0.24
 - Added 'Widgets' on Lock screen and Always On Display
   ※Constraints info in Always On Display
      : Widget usage is not available for burn-in protection in the below cases
        1) when you are using a clock type from Image Clock
        2) when you applied the clock of custom type in ClockFace app

v.5.0.00.15
- GTS error correction

v.5.0.00.14
- Support Smart Switch backup and restore

v.5.0.0.9
- Fixed its edit layout error

V.5.0.0.6
- Update for OneUI 5.0 Foldable Devices

V.5.0.0.3
- Update for OneUI 5.0 Devices

V.3.0.0.32
- Fixed an error which a lock icon keeps visible on quick panel

V3.0.0.30
 - Fixed to remove a internal error (only One UI 5.0 beta device)

V3.0.0.29
- Fixed the shrinked width of music widget
※ LockStar is NOT working in OneUI 5.0 beta binary.

V3.0.0.26
This version fixed 
- the problem that notificaion card is not center aligned
- the problem that notification icon color is not applied when theme is applied


V3.0.0.24
- New UX patch for Galaxy foldable

V3.0.0.6
- Fixed SystemUI exception that occurs when using the list type of app shortcut
- Fixed color errors in notification icons
- Fixed the errors  when used with the old version of ClockFace (2020)
  (Please keep the latest version)

V3.0.0.5
- Fixed the help text size error in lock screen.

V3.0.0.3
Add to change the AOD screen mode. (One UI 4.1)

V2.1.00.29
- Update library for ClockFace support

V2.1.00.27
- Add the reset menu.
- Take charge of a tale visibility guide for musical widgets linked to [Settings> LOCKSCREEN> Widget> Music] in Oneui4.0

V2.1.00.23
- If the status 'Settings> Lock screen> Notification' is disabled while the notification in Lockstar was deactivated, corrected to also update Lockstar settings.

V2.1.00.22
- Fixed the layout error.

V2.1.00.18
- Modified problem that the error occurs while editing the landscape mode.

V2.1.00.17
- Modified problem that the type of clock changed after restarting the device if the theme is applied.
  (Please update the DOA version to version6.2.30)

V2.1.00.16
- You can create a new lock screen style in Galaxy Foldable.

V2.1.00.11
- Support the edit of the Landscape mode.
- Add 3 types for "shortcuts | multiple"]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[7]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Create new Lockscreen style.

You can decorate your lockscreen wallpapers more beautiful.

[Target]
- Android O os 8.0 SAMSUNG devices.

[Language]
- Korean
- English
- Simplified Chinese
- Japanese

<LOCKSTAR:1003:4003>#1]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003266196</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[MultiStar]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.multistar</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003266196/IconImage_20251020052048748_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[5.4.00]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>540000000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>13669415</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS||BLUETOOTH_ADMIN||MEDIA_CONTENT_CONTROL||MANAGE_APP_OPS_MODES||REBOOT||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS_FULL||GET_INTENT_SENDER_INTENT||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS||REGISTER_WINDOW_MANAGER_LISTENERS||MANAGE_ACTIVITY_STACKS||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||REORDER_TASKS||MANAGE_ACTIVITY_TASKS||REAL_GET_TASKS||CONTROL_DISPLAY_BRIGHTNESS||com.system.permission.READ_NOTIFICATIONS||BROADCAST_STICKY||INTERNET||CONTROL_KEYGUARD||STATUS_BAR_SERVICE||USE_FULL_SCREEN_INTENT||BLUETOOTH||WRITE_SETTINGS||ACCESS_KEYGUARD_SECURE_STORAGE</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v10.2.13>
※ Supports devices with One UI 8 and above.
- Application performance optimized.

<10.1.14>
※ Supports One UI 8 and above.  
-Added stickers and emojis.
-Fixed minor bugs.

<v10.0.32>  
※ Supports One UI 8 and above.  
Exclusive 'Launcher Widget' feature for Flip7  
- App Screen Size Conversion: Size conversion icon appears for easy switching between full, landscape, and portrait modes.  
- Portrait Mode Screen Ratio Adjustment: Screen ratio in portrait mode can be adjusted from 16:9 to 21:9 in settings. 

<v10.0.23>
- Support for One UI 8.0
- New feature: FlipShot
  When taking mirror selfies, display stylish photos and messages on the cover screen of Flip devices. (※Available only on Flip devices.)

<v9.1.09>
※ v9.X.X supports One UI 7 devices.
-Fixed cover launcher widget display issues for different app versions.
-Resolved temporary activation of cover game widget in unsupported regions.

<v9.0.15>
- Supports One UI 7
- Expanded 'Split mode maintain' to all models

<v7.2.19>
※Version 7.X.X supports the One UI 6 device. 
1) Launcher Widget in the cover screen
  - Optimized for OneUI 6.1.1 support
  - App icon badge supported
2) Other bug fixes and feature improvements

<v7.1.33>
Additions
- '[Tablet / Fold Device] Provide 'Maintain split mode'' (supports One UI 6.1 and above)

Fixes
- Improved visibility of navigation bar area
- Fixed phenomenon that does not reset when deleting app data

<v7.1.17>
※ (Flip 5 )This version includes modifications related to  'MultiStar > I ♡ Galaxy Foldable  > Launcher widget' 
    1) Support Dual messenger apps
    2) Improved a page loading speed
    3) Fixed errors that specific apps was not loading in a cover screen

<v7.1.05>
- One UI 6 support
- Added Japanese language support

[One UI 5]
<v6.7.3>
- (Flip 5) Limit the number of apps in the launcher widget (up to 200)
- (Flip 5) Add 'Samsung Music' to launcher widget
- (Flip 5) Fixed touch error when running app in launcher widget

<v6.6.1>
- YouTube not being added to Rotate with our best.
- Fixed the phenomenon that the device died during SmartSwitch on B5 devices
- Some apps provided by Samsung as widgets are excluded from the Launcher widget list.
    You can use these apps as default widgets provided.

<v6.5.10>
- Added a cover widget specific to 'Flip 5'
- Added the permission for Smart Switch

<6.4.2>
- Fixed the issue of not running the app set in Cover launch widget

<v6.3.5>
- Fixed errors that corner gesture
- Fixed errors that cover launcher widget

<v6.2.5>
- It supports backup through smart switch.

<v6.1.0>
- Fixed errors that did not execute longPress

<v6.0.12>
※'One UI 5' device is available after this version.

[One UI 4]
<V5.3.6>
- Fixed internal errors that MultiStar did not execute

<V5.2.16>
- Bug fix to Quick launch of the Multi window

<v5.1.20>
- Cover Launcher Widget function (※ Always On Display  v7.1.30.4 or later)
  :Support running the app directly from Galaxy Z Flip 3 cover screen
- Fix some menu descriptions]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Enjoy enhanced Multiwindow experience. 

[Description]
[ One UI 4]
Improved usability on the cover screen of Flip 3. (※ Always On Display  v7.1.30.4 or later)
-Cover launcher widget
 Launch game apps or some media apps directly from the cover screen. (Flip 3 target, you can add up to 5 apps)

Use Multi window without pausing
- You can use several apps at the same time on the Multi window mode without stopping.

[One UI 3 (Android 11)]
Immersive Mode 
- Hide status bar and navigation bar in split screen view
 
The app size stretch to camera hole 
- Open the app by widening the camera area

[One UI 2 (Android 10)]
Enable Multi window to all apps 
- All apps can be launched in a Popup window and split screen.

[One UI 1 (Android 9)]
Ghost Mode 
- When you use Popup Window, you can adjust the transparency of Windows so that you can see what is under the window.

Floating Notification 
- You can receive notifications in the form of icons.


[Target]
- Android O os 8.1~  SAMSUNG devices.

[Language]
- English
- Korean
- Chinese

[Version Code]
<MULTISTAR:1000:10001>
#6]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003488383</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[NavStar]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.systemui.navillera</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003488383/IconImage_20251028052218150_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[4.2.05.35]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>420535000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>5940629</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||READ_MEDIA_IMAGES||READ_MEDIA_VISUAL_USER_SELECTED||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS||READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v8.0.00.47>
- Fixed issue where NavStar icon was not applied in DeX
- Added exception handling for stability and made minor UI adjustments

<v8.0.00.22>
※ v8.x.x supports One UI 8 devices.
-Fixed keyboard layout issue on the flip cover screen:
  Improved UI errors occurring while using NavStar swipe gestures.
-Added 'Side Back Gesture Icon'
 : Customize the arrow image of the back gesture with your own image.


<v8.0.00.4>
- Support One UI 8
- Update UI/UX

<v7.0.00.17>
- Fixed a swipe touch error issue while using the taskbar.
- Fixed an issue where navigation bar buttons were misaligned after rebooting.
- Added an app permissions menu.

<v7.0.00.6>
※Version 7.X.X supports the One UI 7 device.
- Support One UI 7

<v6.1.05.45> 
※Version 6.X.X supports the One UI 6 device. 
- Fixed an issue that occur when upgrading OS.

<v6.1.05.33> 
- Support for the S24 device series
◎ New modifications for One UI 6
[Added]
"Enable extra gesture settings" menu is provided in devices with simplified navigation bar.
: After activating the above menu, you can use the two added gesture options at the following path as in the previous One UI.
   [Path] Settings > Display > Navigation Bar > More Options
    1) "Swipe from bottom" option in Swipe gestures
    2) "Gesture hint" option in Swipe gestures
"Customize side back gesture indicator" function added.

[Not Supported]
-"Background color" is not supported when editing "Icons" with the navigation bar buttons active (a feature included in One UI basic functions).
  : Please use the device's "Color palette" function instead.
-[Galaxy Fold only] "Show task stack" is not supported(a feature included in One UI basic functions).
  : Please use the "Taskbar" instead.
-If the navigation bar button is activated, the following two items are not supported when editing "Icons".
  1) 'Transparency'   2)'Adaptive icon colors'

<One UI 4>
<v4.2.05.35> (One UI 4.1.1)
- Fixed an issue where the gesture mode navigation bar could remain hidden when using DeX.

v4.1.3.20 (One UI 4~)
- Fixed some errors that occurred while using DeX.
V 3.2.4.47 (One UI 3.X)
- Improve usability of 'Show task stack’

V 2.0.0.8 (One UI 2.X)
- Add Volume up/down to button add list]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[7]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Create your own navigation bar.

[Descriptions]
  - You can show and hide the navigation bar.

  - You can change the color of the navigation bar.

  - You can add useful buttons to the navigation bar.

  - You can change the icon of the navigation bar to your favorite image.

   - If you are using gesture mode, you can change the hint background, handle length, and color.

[Language]
- English
- Korean
- Chinese

[Required permission]
-  Storage (Required)
  : The navigation bar images and user settings are saved.

[Version Code]
<NAVSTAR:1001:11000>
#7]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003711875</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Nice Catch]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.app.goodcatch</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003711875/IconImage_20251020051500584_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[8.0.00.1]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>800000001</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>7272234</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||VIBRATE||RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v8.0.00.01>
- Some minor improvements.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[9]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Got tired of mysterious vibration on your phone?

Nice Catch is made to let you know which application starts the vibrations and annoys you.

And it also reports :
 - Ringer mode
 - Call mode
 - Toast
 - Advertisement screen
 - Sudden wake-up of your phone.
 - Changed setting value (Since One UI 2.0)
 - Muted media volume (Since One UI 3.1.1)
 - Changed accessibility setting value (Since One UI 5.0)
 - Blocked notifications (Since One UI 6.0)
 - Muted notifications (Since One UI 6.0)
 - Sounds (Since One UI 6.0)

[Target]
- SAMSUNG devices with Android P OS(ver 9.0) or above.

[Language]
- Korean
- English
- Simplified Chinese
- Japanese

[How to Use]
Press "Vibration history" in app's main screen and you get a list of application that made vibrations.
(please make sure that the switch is enabled before use.)

#GoodLockFriends #3]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003926817</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Nice Shot]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.app.captureplugin</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003926817/IconImage_20251020052114715_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[2.0.06]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>200600000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>13632446</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||STATUS_BAR_SERVICE||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v2.3.06>
- Add 'Share to GTS' menu in more option
- Fix settings not applied issues in some devices

<v2.3.02>
- Support GTS (Galaxy To Share)
- Show selected color in the color selection menu as text

<v2.2.01>
- Added Japanese language support]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[[One UI 5]
○ Screen capture : Delete the "Do not copy image to the clipboard when saving" setting
                         (Do not support saving the clipboard when capturing from One UI 5)
○ Screen recording : Delete the "Selfie video options -> Selfie video size" setting
                           (※ Please use the settings in "Settings -> Advanced features -> Screenshots and screen recorder" of the device.)

[One UI 4]
* Each menu offered will appear differently on the specifications supported by the device.
○ Screen capture : Provides settings such as activating the delete button immediately when capturing the screen, not saving it to the clipboard, and turning off the magnet effect after capturing.

○ Screen recording : You can set various backgrounds when shooting self-videos, and you can automatically run the Do Not Disturb mode when recording screens.

[Before Q os]
Provides a variety of screenshot options.
(Some functions are available only on smart capture support devices.)
Provides a variety of screen shot options.(Some functions are available only on smart capture support terminals.)
- Save Format: Change the screen shot format to PNG or JPG.
- Automatic removal of system UI: Remove indicator and navigation bar and save.
- #Tag: We recommend Tag for easy classification after smart capture.
- Automatic deletion after sharing: It will be automatically deleted from the Smart Capture toolbar when it is not saved in Gallery.
- Screen Recording: Provides screen recording function.

* Note 10 Series are pre-loaded with 'screen recorder' and 'tags', so it is no longer supported.]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000004085658</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[NotiStar]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.systemui.notilus</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000004085658/IconImage_20251020051748478_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[8.0.33.0]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>803300000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>10369642</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>READ_WALLPAPER_INTERNAL||SUBSTITUTE_NOTIFICATION_APP_NAME||READ_MEDIA_VIDEO||MANAGE_ACTIVITY_STACKS||FOREGROUND_SERVICE||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS||READ_MEDIA_IMAGES||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||VIBRATE||INTERNAL_SYSTEM_WINDOW||MANAGE_ACTIVITY_TASKS||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS_FULL||SET_PROCESS_LIMIT||CONTROL_KEYGUARD||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||MANAGE_USERS||READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v8.0.33.00>  
- App performance optimization.  
- Fixed to not allow spaces when entering keywords.  
 (Spaces were causing filtering issues, which have been resolved.)  
※ Spaces in previously created filter keywords were not automatically removed, so please manually check and adjust them.  
※ Please restart your device after installing the new version.



<v8.0.17.0>
- Supports One UI 8.0

<v7.0.17.0> 
Fixed the issue of notification permissions being reset after rebooting.

<v7.0.15.0>
- Supports One UI 7.0
- Fixes notification duplication issue
- Resolves layout problems
- Stores app notifications in work profile (One UI 5~)

<v6.0.92.0>
- Supports One UI 6.1.1
- Changed widget logic on cover screen
- Added selection of notification screen background color on lock screen
- Fixed an issue where receiving notifications with large images caused errors

<v6.0.32.00>
- Fix Layout bug
- Support Flip5 cover widget
- Fix bug that lockscreen icon is remain on home screen
- Show bigger image if notification has image
- Long press notification to save image

<v5.3.73.0>
-Support for OneUI 6.0
-Added support for Japanese language
※ Supports displaying app icons to run Flip5 coverscreen. Please use MultiStar Launcher Widget

v5.2.54.00
- Fix P OS FC

v5.2.53.00
- Support Widget
- Set app unable to clear notifications (Support after One UI 5.1.1)
- Sync with lock state when using NotiStar on Lock screen
- Support Dark mode

v5.1.24.00
- Layout bug fix
- Support smart switch (settings only)
- Fix duplicated entry point view on lock screen

v5.1.08.00
- OneUI 5.0 support
- Fixed an error related to the lock screen entry point icon
- Other UI bug fixes

v4.2.53.0
 - 'One UI 4' device is available after this version.

v3.1.33.0
 - Fix some layout errors (ex. permission window, RTL etc)

v3.1.31.1
 - Add permission notice

v3.1.30.0
 1. Show the alert message when the lock screen hide the content setting is turned on.
 2. Fix Database searching issue with special characters.
 (Search might not work properly if some special characters are included in the filter.)
 3. Fixed other minor bugs.

v3.1.24.0
 1. Fixed an issue where the entry point disappears from the lock screen intermittently
 2. Fixed minor bugs

v3.1.19.1
- We now support the following:
 1. Landscape mode for all layouts
 2. Copy & Share with long-press a notification
 3. Keyword highlighting when searching notifications

- The following fixed: 
 1. App icons of saved notifications turned white
 2. Other performance issues

v2.1.22.20
- Fixed the issue that our lock screen handler keeps on home screen.
- Support the landscape mode. (Except the menu, 'Start icon settings on Lock screen', which will be improved later)

v2.1.22.9
- Fixed Issue that the NotiStar freezes when the screen is scrolled while many notifications are coming in.
- Fixed Issue that LockScreen handler disappear.

v2.1.22.6
- A notification filter's whole characters will be shown (without ... mark). (the filter's limit is 8 characters) 
- Fixed the late response after 'clear all' action of notifications
- Fixed the dark theme issue with clear all dialog 
- Fixed LockScreen handler's resolution issue

v2.1.22.1
- Add timestamp at Notification Card
- Fixed LockScreen handler's visibility issue
 
v2.1.21.6
- Improve sluggish issue while multiwindow( like pop-view and split view) of NotiStar.
- Fixed the filter sorting issue.
- Fixed the issue that NotiStar was not running after update.
- Minor change of UI.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[NotiStar is new notification management service

[Description]
NotiStar is new notification management service
By using this, You can manage many of the notifications you have received so far
In addition, you can search for delivered notifications or categorize them as you like.
All of these notifications are always there before you delete them.
We are trying to make fresh experience for users.

Tip: If you tap & hold the NotiStar menu in Good Lock app, its shortcut icon is created on the home screen

[Target]
- Android T OS 13.0 SAMSUNG devices.
- Android S OS 12.0 SAMSUNG devices.
- Android R OS 11.0 SAMSUNG devices.
- Android Q OS 10.0 SAMSUNG devices.
- Android P OS 9.0 SAMSUNG devices.

[Language]
- Korean
- English
- Chinese

[Optional permission]
- Storage (Optional)
  : When editing icons accessible on the lock screen, Storage is accessed to show the wallpaper on the preview screen.

[Version Code]
<NOTISTAR:2001:9001>
#GoodLockFriends]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003036952</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[One Hand Operation +]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.sidegesturepad</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003036952/IconImage_20250916231633510_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[7.4.19.0]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>741900000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>8200180</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>MODIFY_PHONE_STATE||MEDIA_CONTENT_CONTROL||START_TASKS_FROM_RECENTS||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS_FULL||SET_PROCESS_LIMIT||MANAGE_NOTIFICATIONS||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS||WAKE_LOCK||ACCESS_WIFI_STATE||MANAGE_USERS||PACKAGE_USAGE_STATS||BLUETOOTH_SCAN||MODIFY_DAY_NIGHT_MODE||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||INTERNAL_SYSTEM_WINDOW||MANAGE_ACTIVITY_TASKS||READ_PROJECTION_STATE||CONTROL_DISPLAY_BRIGHTNESS||MONITOR_INPUT||DEVICE_POWER||START_ACTIVITIES_FROM_BACKGROUND||CHANGE_WIFI_STATE||INJECT_EVENTS||RETRIEVE_WINDOW_CONTENT||BLUETOOTH_CONNECT||UPDATE_DEVICE_STATS||CHANGE_OVERLAY_PACKAGES||REMOVE_TASKS||FLASHLIGHT||FOREGROUND_SERVICE||EXPAND_STATUS_BAR||BLUETOOTH_ADMIN||RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED||READ_FRAME_BUFFER||START_ANY_ACTIVITY||BLUETOOTH_ADVERTISE||STOP_APP_SWITCHES||REQUEST_IGNORE_BATTERY_OPTIMIZATIONS||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||MANAGE_ACTIVITY_STACKS||STATUS_BAR||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||VIBRATE||SET_ACTIVITY_WATCHER||REORDER_TASKS||READ_PRIVILEGED_PHONE_STATE||REAL_GET_TASKS||BIND_APPWIDGET||SET_ORIENTATION||STATUS_BAR_SERVICE||FORCE_STOP_PACKAGES||NETWORK_SETTINGS||BLUETOOTH||WRITE_SETTINGS</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<Version 8.5.11>
- Fix brightness control malfunction issue in Quick tools.
- Bug fixes and stability improvements.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[9]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Control your phone or tablet more easily with just one hand.

With this app you can easily use your device with your thumb gesture.

When the feature is set, a thin gesture handle is added to the left/right side of the screen. 
Swipe this handle to execute the defined functions. The default function is the most frequently used back button.

You can set various functions for horizontal/diagonal up/down diagonal gestures.
Once you get used to using short swipe gestures, you can set more features for long swipe gestures.

Depending on the size of your hand, the thickness of your thumb, or the shape of the bumper case you are using, different handle settings are provided to optimize gesture recognition.

The handle receives the user's touch event on top of the running app. It can interfere with running applications. Therefore, it is recommended to set the handle as thin as possible for gesture recognition. 

If the touch interference is severe with running application such as game, you can set [App exceptions] in [Advanced Settings], then the gesture handles will not work when the app is running.

Currently available functions are as follows, and we plan to provide additional function upgrades.

 - Back key
 - Home key
 - Recent key
 - Menu key
 - Apps screen
 - Previous app
 - Forward ( web browser )
 - Open notification panel 
 - Open quick panel 
 - Screen off 
 - Close app
 - Flashlight
 - Split screen view
 - Assistance app 
 - Finder search
 - Screenshot 
 - Show/hide navigation bar
 - Floating navigation buttons
 - Pull screen down
 - One-handed mode
 - Power key menu
 - Home screen shortcuts 
 - Start application 
 - Task switcher 
 - Virtual touch pad
 - Quick tools

Enjoy the convenience of gestures on your phone and tablet with this app.

Thank you.

#GoodLockFriends #5]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000005198690</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Pentastic]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.pentastic</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000005198690/IconImage_20250902090716667_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[1.1.14.1]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>111400001</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>26094917</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS||WRITE_SETTINGS</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<2.3.09>
- Modify to allow only on devices supporting Air Command
- Applied stabilization code

<2.3.08>
※This version supports One UI 7.0 and later devices.
- Applied stabilization code of One UI 7.0.
- Applied new Feature (Custom Floating Icon)

<2.2.04>
- Fixed an issue that does not change the style of the air command
- Fixed the FC issue on Chinese model

<2.2.03>
- Applied stabilization code of One UI 6.0.
※This version supports One UI 6.0 and later devices.

<2.0.5.3>
Supported Air command Compact mode within the S Pen settings

<1.1.14.1>
Fixed an error of the app ternimation in OneUI 5 device.

<1.1.14>
- Link with wallpaper and sticker resources 

<1.1.11>
- Support Air command background
* This feature works above Air command v5.6.21]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[9]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Add your uniqueness to S pen with Pentastic!
Switch to Air Command that is more convenient for you to use.
You can set yourself the shape of the S Pen Hover Pointer, the sound made when you pull out or put in the pen.
If you tap the screen twice while pressing S Pen button, you can run the preset features immediately.

[Key features]
Change the form of Air Command
Change the shape of S Pen Hover Pointer
Change the sound of S Pen
Set double tap to shortcut by pressing S Pen

* OneUI2.1 supports only 'Change the form of Air Command' feature.

#Pentastic, #SPenThemes, #AircommandThemes, #SPenPointer, #SPenSound, #GoodLockFriends #0]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003084407</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[QuickStar]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.qstuner</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003084407/IconImage_20251020051916102_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[6.4.08.45]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>640845000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>15320543</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||SYSTEM_ALERT_WINDOW||WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v9.0.00.01>
※ Version v9.X.X supports devices running One UI 7 and above.
- Supports One UI 8 devices.
- Fixed other bugs.

<v8.1.02.24>
 - Fixed the problem that the clock position is forcibly set to the middle in a model with no middle option
 - Improve app stability

<v8.1.02.21>
 - Improve app stability

<v8.0.02.18>
 - Support One UI 7

<v7.4.07.56>
 - Improve app stability

<v7.3.06.50>
 - Support hiding mobile hotspot icon
 - Improve app stability

v7.2.06.35
 - Support to change the format of the date displayed on the indicator clock (One UI 6.1)
 - Change the way to connect Theme Park (One UI 6.0 or higher)
     ※ Please install the latest version of the Theme Park(v1.1.00.8 or higher)
 - Stabilize "Quick settings instant access"

v7.1.03.22
 - Fix the problem of Quick settings instant access

v7.0.03.20
 - Support for OneUI 6.0
 - Supports changing quick setting button grid inside the app (OneUI 6.0)
 - Added GTS support of "Apply color palette to notification icons" (OneUI 5.1.1 or higher)
 - Added Japanese support.
 ※ "Show notifications by last update" and "Quick settings instant access" ON / OFF settings are provided as device functions from One UI 6.0 and removed from the app

v6.4.08.45
 - Fix the problem that the app does not open

v6.4.08.43
 - Support hiding icons of modes and device care in "Visibility of Indicator Icons"
 - Improve app stability

v6.3.06.31
 - Support Smart Switch for the following functions (OneUI4.0 or later)
     • Show notifications by last update
     • Show Quick button grid
     • Open Quick panel directly

v6.2.05.27
 - Fix a problem that its setting value was deactivated automatically at times

v6.1.05.20
 - Support seconds clock on panel (OneUI5)
 - Support date clock on indicator (OneUI5)
 - Improve app stability.

v5.2.00.03
 - Shorten the entry path for 'Open Quick panel directly' menu.
 - Supported a guide overlay on statubar for the area of 'Quick Setting' and 'Notification'

v5.1.00.08
 - Fixed the initialization of the position set via 'Open Quick panel directly' after reboot.
 - Fixed the turned-off of the volume item after reentry in 'Visibility of Indicator Icons'.
 - Removed the unavailable in One UI 4, ex. 'Use sections' in 'Show notifications by last update'

v5.1.00.02
 - Fixed not to show mute icon in One UI 4

v5.0.00.00
 - Available in One UI 4 (based on Android 12)

v4.2.00.20
 - Remove unnecessary permission
 - Fix the layout error

v4.2.00.17
 - Fixed the error that "Show notifications by the last update" was initialized, after the device reboot
 - Fixed the issue where  QuickStar values were not restored after Good Lock update
 - Support  'Middle' position in clock setting in Foldable devices

v4.2.00.15
 - Added new menu, "Style your own Quick Panel"

v4.1.04.06
 - Fixed an error not-restored a feature like Quick button grid after device reboot
  (※ After using DEX, the unrecovered issue can be improved through SW update in device)

v4.1.04.05
 - Support VPN icon in "Visibility of Indicator Icons"
 - Change app icon and improve GUI]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[7]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Customize your special Quickpanel.

[Description]
- Make a simple status bar.

<One UI 5>
 ※ Support seconds clock on panel.
 ※ Support date clock on indicator.

<One UI 4>
 ※ Improve app stability.

[Detail Description]
QuickStar is QuickPanel Star a SystemUI service app for early adopters.
QuickStar is a plugin application for customizing SAMSUNG SystemUI Quicksettings components.
By using this, You can change layouts and settings of Google Basic Quickpanel which is blocked by Samsung and can handle new features of Notification that QuickStar provides.
We are trying to make a fresh experience for users.

[Target]
- Android 8 or higher devices

[Language]
- Korean
- English
- Chinese
- Japanese

[Version Code]
<SLIMINDICATOR:1003:9000>
#2]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000005563964</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Routines +]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.app.routineplus</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000005563964/IconImage_20251020051533204_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[1.0.60]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>106007000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>20096225</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>FOREGROUND_SERVICE_SPECIAL_USE||WAKE_LOCK||POST_NOTIFICATIONS||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||RECORD_AUDIO||INTERNET||FOREGROUND_SERVICE||RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED||WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||REORDER_TASKS||CAMERA||READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE||READ_PHONE_STATE</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v1.1.18>
-Just in Routine feature added (Supports One UI 7 and above):
Create routines that can be reminded by Now Brief or notifications at specific times.
※ Only available in Now Brief on One UI 8.0 and above.
※ Otherwise, notifications will be used instead.
- Fixed minor bugs.


<v1.0.75>
- Bug fixes

<v1.0.68>
- Bug fixes and stabilization code applied

<v1.0.60>
- Bug fixes and stabilization code applied
- Add Routine Gallery for OneUI 7.0

<v1.0.52>
-Fixed the "Button action" error.
-Updated the Routine SDK version to 3.1.9.

<v1.0.49>
1) The following conditions of 'Routine +' are not available in devices with simplified navigation bar.
     - A combination of 'Home' button and 'Touch and hold' among options of "Button action"
2) Fixed bugs.

<v1.0.44>
- Japanese language support
- Fixed bugs

<v1.0.38>
 - Fixed touch macro action error in One UI 5

<v1.0.34>
 - Added touch macro stop action


<v1.0.33>
- Fixed FC issue during saved button action.

<v1.0.30>
-Added permission notification screen

<v1.0.28>
 - Routine + multi-condition setting error fix

<v1.0.27>
S pen action
- Change the menu name (Air action > S pen action)
- Fix issues where unsupported air actions are provided on some devices

Touch macro
- Support to create an touch macro without specifying app

Others
- Fix no Keyboard issues during some operation
- Fix FC issue related to library compatibility

<v1.0.25>
Launch Routines +.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Add advanced features to Modes and Routines so you can make more powerful routines.
Get additional features for your Modes and Routines.
 
 Features:
 ● Added conditions
  - Unlock with fingerprint, S Pen action(Using S Pen), Button action
 ● Added actions
  - Read text aloud, Arrow key, Touch macro
 ● Share (Share via QR code, Export routines, Import saved routines)
* Only available to Routines + users.
 
Supported languages:
English, Korean, Chinese
 
[Optional permission]
- Camera (Optional)
  : Accesses the Camera to share routines by scanning QR codes.

* Please install Android OS 11 and One UI 3.1 or later for a pleasant experience while using Routines +.
* Feature availability may vary by device model/OS version.

<ROUTINE_PLUS:3000:99999>]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000003206291</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Sound Assistant]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.soundassistant</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000003206291/IconImage_20251020051522530_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[6.1.00.9]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>610000009</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>26794146</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>MODIFY_PHONE_STATE||FOREGROUND_SERVICE||BLUETOOTH_ADMIN||FOREGROUND_SERVICE_SPECIAL_USE||MEDIA_CONTENT_CONTROL||RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED||ACCESS_NOTIFICATION_POLICY||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS_FULL||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WAKE_LOCK||POST_NOTIFICATIONS||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||VIBRATE||RECORD_AUDIO||DEVICE_POWER||MODIFY_AUDIO_ROUTING||INTERNET||SYSTEM_APPLICATION_OVERLAY||MODIFY_AUDIO_SETTINGS||BLUETOOTH||BLUETOOTH_CONNECT||WRITE_SETTINGS</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v8.1.00.6>
Note: Version 8.x.x supports devices running One UI 8.
- Applied One UI 8.0 UI to my own volume panel
- Applied stabilization code

<v7.2.00.2>
- Apply essential accessibility requirements
- Applied stabilization code

<v7.1.00.7>
Note: Version 7.x.x supports devices running One UI 7.
- Added 'Maintain media volume while using navigation' option
  (Please note that this feature may behave differently depending on specific navigation apps.)
- Applied One UI 7.0 UI to my own volume panel

<v6.1.00.9>
- Deleted 'Reverse stereo' function for Fold 6/Flip 6.
   (*Reason: Due to changes in system sound processing methods, stable functionality cannot be guaranteed.)

<v6.1.00.7>
- Supports One UI 6.1.1
  1) Added Galaxy Buds 3 icon
  2) Equalizer preset for 6.1.1 reflected
- Applied stabilization code

<v5.2.0.1>
- Apply stabilization code

<v5.1.0.10>
- Apply stabilization code
- Fixed the problem that app volume setting is initialized after rebooting
- Fixed dex volume panel display error

<v5.1.0.6>
- Flex Volume UI (Support from One UI 5)
Choose effect, texture, size and control type.

- Dual App Volume View (Support from One UI 5)
When the volume of the app is not 100%, it appears next to the main volume. (app volume, media volume)

- Customized voice effects (Support from One UI 6)
Provide custom effect creation option.

<v4.5.0.2>
- Fixed force close on One UI 4.1

<v4.5.0.1>
- <Flip5 only> Add volume panel custom on cover screen
- Provides 'voice mask effect' panel to edge panel
- Providing a confirmation pop-up when applying a voice mask

<v4.4.0.5>
- Fix icon error when connecting Buds
- Goodlock search function support

<v4.4.0.3>
- Stabilization of GTS support

<v4.4.0.1>
- T os compatible processing

<v4.3.0.1>
- Improved visibility of EQ panel in dark mode.
- Added default activation option to voice changer feature.

<v4.2.01>
- A color preset is provided on the volume panel
- Apply volume panel theme to DeX mode (From OneUI 4.0)
- Added new feature that provide various effects to the microphone in game chat and recording app (From OneUI 4.0)

<v4.1.06.0>
- Fixed an issue where the app sometimes quits during boot up

<v4.1.06.0>
- Fixed the volume panel BG error after applying a theme

<v4.1.05.0>
It is compatible with OneUI4.0 (Android 12)

<v4.1.00.7>
Default to display volume level in the volume bar
Added volume panel position change function to menu
Other operation stabilization

<v4.1.00.2>
Restore the floating button
Volume panel customizing - Interworking with Theme Park
Fixed the problem that concert hall doesn't work intermittently.
Stabilize other operation

<v3.6.07.2>
Fixed FC issue while using volume panel theme.

<v3.6.07.1>
- OneUI 3
Added OneUI 3 Style Volume Panel color.

<v3.5.14.1>
- OneUI 2
The app icon has been changed.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs ]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Advanced sound utility for your Galaxy.

The sound utility available on the galaxy series
Provides various convenience functions related to audio
※ How to use : https://youtu.be/Z5mrB4ryKjE
※ Some devices may not be supported

- Flux Volume UI (Support from One UI 5)
Choose effect, texture, size and control type.

- Dual App Volume View (Support from One UI 5)
When the volume of the app is not 100%, it appears next to the main volume.

- Customized voice effects (Support from One UI 6)
Provide custom effect creation option.

- Allow you to control the media volume instead of ringtone when pressing the volume keys
- Support individual application volume (You can control the volume of music and games differently)  
- 150 steps of fine volume and support Floating Equalizer(EQ)
- Create and activate personalize sound settings
- Support mono audio and left / right balance
- Touch the app volume icon in the floating dialog to mute/unmute and long click to enter the app.
- Default volume step when pressing volume button can now be changed
- Audio output of an application can now be switched between Bluetooth or speaker via floating volume dialog
- EQ settings can now be saved and shared
- Ability to swap left and right sounds on headphones
- Ability to hear ringtone, notification, and alarm sounds only through headphones when headphone is connected
- Favorite media app : Select an app to control music when you press multimedia keys.
- Supports concert hall effect
- Adjust previous/next song with volume key
- When an earphone or Bluetooth is connected, you can select where the ringtone, notification, and alarm sound will be played.
- Dual app sound is extended to multi sound so all apps can be played simultaneously
- Provide vibration effect of the volume panel theme slider according to whether the vibration feedback of the -default setting app is activated
- Apps that appear once in the app volume slider are maintained for a certain period of time even if they do not sound
- Add an option that reverse the ability to switch to the previous/next song through volume key long press
- More sound effects menu

#GoodLockFriends]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000004623161</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Theme Park]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.themedesigner</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000004623161/IconImage_20251020051305142_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[1.0.09.73]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>100973000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>23800964</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>READ_WALLPAPER_INTERNAL||REMOVE_TASKS||PACKAGE_USAGE_STATS||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||FOREGROUND_SERVICE||QUERY_ALL_PACKAGES||RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED||REAL_GET_TASKS||INTERNET||GET_INTENT_SENDER_INTENT||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WAKE_LOCK||SET_WALLPAPER</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<Version: 1.1.01.31>
- UI improvements and bug fixes
- Enhanced app stability

<Version: 1.1.01.25>  
- Improved UI and fixed bugs

<Version: 1.1.01.23>  
- Added the following effects to the icon pack: Basic, Film Grain, Duotone, Glass, and Gradient  
- Improved UI and fixed bugs

<Version: 1.1.01.06>
 - Stability improvements

<Version: 1.1.01.05>
- Expanded selection of wallpapers and stickers
- UI improvements
- Changed folder and app drawer icons (One UI 7)

<Version : 1.0.09.73>
Fixed an issue where themes created with Theme Park couldn't be installed.
※This version is only applicable to devices with One UI 5 or earlier.

<Version: 1.1.00.23>
-Improved visibility error after applying keyboard themes 
-Enhanced app stability

<Version : 1.1.00.21>
- Customizable app icon shapes
- Improved app stability and fixed minor bugs

<Version: 1.1.0.18>
1. Modified to allow only wallpaper changes without theme initialization
2. Improvement of keyboard keycap errors
3. Fixation of blank page appearing in more wallpaper
4. App stability and other error improvements

<Version: 1.1.0.14>
 - Code updated to support One UI 6.1.1
 - Bug fix for app icons transparency issue
 - Improved quick panel color
 - Stability improvements and other minor bug fixes


<Version: 1.1.0.09>
 - Fixed  an app crash when creating an icon pack
 - Fixed  minor bugs like an applied color error.

<Version: 1.1.00.08> 
: We changed our previous 'APK installation method' to the devices' 'theme application method (Color palette)'. This results in the following improvements:

-Faster theme creation and application speed.
-The ability to edit and overwrite themes.
- Automatically reflects new icons for newly installed apps based on the current icon pack being used.

Due to changes in the theme application method, some features are no longer available:
 - Theme Park > More > 
    1) Remove 'App's theme settings'
    2) Remove 'Color palette change'
 - Theme Park > Theme > 'Keyboard' (or Theme Park > 'Keyboard') > 'Keycap Style' deleted
 - Theme Park > Theme > 'Home Screen' > Folder Shape Change deleted
※ Please make sure to install the latest version of both QuickStar and Keys Cafe that work together with Theme Park as well.


<Version: 1.0.9.72> 
- ONE UI 6 support


<Version: 1.0.9.62> 
- UI improvements 
- Fixed coloring issues


<Version: 1.0.9.60> 
- Adding the default theme to the list of themes and icons 

<Version: 1.0.9.57> 
- Ability to change Color Palette colors 
- Other bug fixes and usability improvements

<Version: 1.0.9.55> 
- Fix layout broken issue of quickpanel preview
- Squarcle icon size adjust
- Other bug fixes and usability improvements

<Version: 1.0.9.50> 
- Fixed a bug that prevented some themes from being exported on GTS
- Added the ability to change the background color of the brightness bar in the quick panel (T OS)
- Other bug fixes and usability improvements

<Version: 1.0.9.48>
- Fixed issue with themes not being created on R OS
- Removed transparency limit for notification background color in quickpanel
- Other bug fixes and usability improvements

<Version: 1.0.9.46>
-Fixed issues with some UI not being visible and quick panel preview

<Version: 1.0.9.43>
- One UI 5 Quick Panel Preview Update
- Fix errors and theme colors

<Version: 1.0.9.41>
-One UI 5.0 theme support
-Improve Quick Panel Bright Bar Custom UI

<Version: 1.0.9.32>
- Support to change All Apps icon
- Fix color picker to extract color from image
- Fix FC that occurs when there are many installed apps during icon pack authoring

<Version: 1.0.9.29>
-Fixed theme colors such as keyboards, galleries, and home.
-Fixed a bug of icon pack function.]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Theme Park is a service to create a theme and install it quickly and easily.

It extracts dominant colors from wallpaper and creates theme automatically based on user's style and the colors. Users can see the final appearance from preview screens. Create your own theme that can express your personality!



Main feature

▣ Creating a theme from a background image
  ■ The theme color is automatically determined from the background image.
  ■ You can change the colors of the style.
  ■ The theme include colors for light mode theme and dark mode.
  ■ You can edit the color of the icon or the color of the tray. (OneUI 2.0)
  ■ You can apply icon packs downloaded from the theme store. (OneUI 2.5)
  ■ You can change the color of the keyboard and key cap images. (OneUI 2.5)
  ■ You can customize the quick panel as you wish. (OneUI 3.0)

▣ Creating a theme for samsung keyboard (OneUI 2.5, with KeysCafe)
  ■ You can apply a keyboard theme separately from the main theme.
  ■ You can easily create a keyboard theme by selecting a basic color and style.
  ■ You can customize keycaps and text colors to your own color or image.
  ■ Templates for key cap is provided.

▣ Deciding whether to apply the theme for each app (OneUI 2.5)
  ■ You can decide whether to apply the theme for each app.

▣ Creating a theme for quick panel (OneUI 3.0)
  ■ You can apply the theme for quick panel separately from the main theme.
  ■ You can easily create a theme for a quick panel by selecting a basic color and style.
  ■ You can change the color of each part of the quick panel.

▣ Tablet device support (OneUI 3.0)
  ■ You can use the theme park on tablet devices with OneUI 3.0 or higher.
  ■ Landscape mode is also supported on devices with sw700 or higher.



Cautions
  ■ Previews could be not matched with actual screen that the theme is applied.
  ■ The applications supported by theme can be varied based on version.
  ■ Some features may not be available depending on the Android version.


Permissions (Required)
  To provide this service, following permission are needed.
  ■ Photos and videos (Storage): Theme Park uses an image file in your device to find dominant colors and create theme that has harmonious colors.

#GoodLockFriends #2]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<appInfo>
		<productID>000005212031</productID>
		<productName><![CDATA[Wonderland]]></productName>
		<appId>com.samsung.android.wonderland.wallpaper</appId>
		<iconImgURL>https://img.samsungapps.com/productNew/000005212031/IconImage_20251020051413784_NEW_WAP_ICON_512_512.png</iconImgURL>
		<currencyUnit>€</currencyUnit>
		<price>0.00</price>
		<discountPrice>0.00</discountPrice>
		<discountFlag>N</discountFlag>
		<versionName><![CDATA[1.6.16]]></versionName>
		<versionCode>161600000</versionCode> 
		<realContentSize>88597011</realContentSize>
		<restrictedAge>0</restrictedAge>
		<permission>BIND_WALLPAPER||INTERACT_ACROSS_USERS||com.wssnps.permission.COM_WSSNPS||READ_MEDIA_IMAGES||VIBRATE||RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED||AMBIENT_WALLPAPER||ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE||WAKE_LOCK||com.android.homescreen.home.permission.preview_image||SET_WALLPAPER||READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE||SET_WALLPAPER_COMPONENT||MAINLINE_NETWORK_STACK</permission>
			<updateDescription><![CDATA[<v1.6.16>
- Improved battery efficiency when using dynamic wallpapers.

<v1.6.15>
[New]
-Blur Effect: Added vertical and horizontal blur options for lock screen transition effects.

[Improvements]
-Fixed an issue where the Wonderland wallpaper on the Flip cover screen could not be reset to another wallpaper.
-Updated user interface for improved usability.
-Resolved intermittent issues with video playback and animations freezing.
-Fixed an issue where the wallpaper setting was occasionally disabled on Fold devices.
-Addressed intermittent app crashes during image and video resource loading.
<v1.6.07>
※ This update is available only for devices with One UI 7 or higher.
- Set wallpaper exclusively on the lock screen
- See real-time previews of Wonderland backgrounds while setting wallpapers
- Auto-adjusts font colors based on chosen wallpaper for better readability
- Fixed issue where video files were unable to be added

<v1.5.21>
- Fixed an issue with displaying the AOD image setting menu for a unique lock effect on certain unsupported devices.
- Fixed an exception that occurred when selecting the AOD image setting menu.
- UI and color theme changes to enhance usability.

<v1.5.16>
- Fixed an issue where the wallpaper gets initialized during operation on some devices.
- Fixed an issue where some settings are missing during backup/restore through Smart Switch.
- Fixed an issue where the wallpaper is displayed incorrectly or particles do not operate in certain situations.
- Fixed an issue where dark mode is not supported in some UIs.
- Improved usability of some UIs.

<v1.5.09>
- Support new lockscreen effect "Fluid"
- Fix issue that wallpaper reset to default on foldable devices
- Adjust UI for better usability

<v1.5.05>
- Support fullscreen AOD (Only Galaxy S24 Series)
- Support new lockscreen effect "Slide"
- Improve usability to prevent conflicts between settings from wonderland and LockStar (Since OneUI 6.1)
- Include bug fixes related to UI and runtime exception

<v1.4.08>
- Fixed the forced termination problem that occurs in some scenarios.
- Fixed a problem where Dark Mode was not properly supported in some UIs.
- Adjusted the color of some UIs.

<v1.4.05>
- Supports AOD transition of Galaxy Z Fold / Flip device. (Some devices with OneUI 6.0 or higher)
- Remove unnecessary masking effects when setting dynamic animation options for Galaxy Z Fold / Flip devices.
- Change the location of the image setting button and the effect selection button.
- Fix the issue where the setting is reset if the button is not pressed on the image setting screen.

<v1.4.04>
- Support transition effect from Always On Display (Some devices that support OneUI6.0 or higher)
* After applying the lock screen transition effect, changing the settings related to Always On Display and lock screen through settings, LockStar, ClockFace, etc. may release the transition effect.
- Add new 3 effects (Hexagon, Slice, Flip)
- Change chooser UI for image and effect
- Adjust default configuration value of effect

<v1.3.04>
- Supports Flex Window wallpaper setting through MultiStar's LauncherWidget. (Galaxy Z Flip5 Only)
- Improving the transition effect to respond smoothly.
- Fixed an issue that shows an incorrect image frame in some effects when screen off
- Various bug fixes and usability improvements are included

<v1.3.01>
- Supports new type of wallpaper that includes transition effect when user turns on the screen
- For Fold device, users can set different wallpaper for each display
- For Fold and Flip device, users can connect transition effects on folding angle through dynamic animation option

<v1.2.30>
- Solve the problem that the video does not play normally

<v1.2.29>
- Support wallpaper sharing through Galaxy To Share

<v1.2.27>
- Support OneUI 5.0]]></updateDescription>
		<sellerName><![CDATA[Good Lock Labs]]></sellerName>
		<categoryName><![CDATA[Good Lock]]></categoryName>
		<averageRating><![CDATA[8]]></averageRating><description><![CDATA[Create moving wallpapers and stunning lock screen effects.

Activate your hidden artist's touch with Wonderland and become a creator. Transform both your home screen and lock screen experience. 
Create motion effects for your wallpaper that respond to device movement, add beautiful particle effects like rain and snow, and design seamless transition animations between your lock screen and Always On Display (AOD).
Use our intuitive tools and various presets to easily create your personalized dynamic wallpaper and lock screen experience.

[Key Features]
- Motion wallpaper creation: Set up motion effects that respond to your device's gyroscope
- Particle effects: Choose from 5 presets (rain, snow, bubbles, sparkles, spread) with full customization
- Lock screen transitions: 12 unique transition effects for seamless lock screen to AOD experience
- Layer-based editing: Combine multiple elements with independent effects
- Real-time preview: See changes instantly before applying

[Supported Languages]
- Korean, English, Chinese Simplified, Japanese

[Notice for application's permission]
Wonderland uses these permissions
- Required permissions
Photos and Videos : Access images and videos for wallpaper creation.

#wonderland #livewallpaper #dynamicwallpaper #lockscreeneffects #alwaysondisplay #particleeffects #motioneffects #customwallpaper #personalizedlockscreen]]></description>
		</appInfo>
	<serverType>PRD</serverType>
</result>